Guide to the James R. Houck papers.
Houck, James R. papers.
- Series I. General Documents
  - Letters to and From Martin, 1977 (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Letters, 1981 (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - Sky and Telescope Magazine, 1977-10 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Grant Proposal for 3He Bolometer System, 1978-1981 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Grant Proposal for Renewed Support, 1976-1980 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Grant Proposal for Renewed Support, 1974-1981 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Grant Proposal for Renewed Support, 1977-1979 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Grant Proposal for Renewed Support, 1980-1983 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Monthly Reports, 1986-1987 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Misc. Photos, Undated (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Letters of Application, 1980-1981 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Washington C-141 Meeting Materials, 1981 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Center for Radiophysics and Space Research Documents, 1976-1979 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Fred's Panel, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Satellite Papers, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - He3 Proposal, 1976-1980 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - MOSFET(?) Proposal, 1979 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - C-141 Users Group, 1979 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Press Releases, 1985 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Letters, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Sloan Foundation Documents, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - AMES Detectors, 1977-1980 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - MM(Millimeter?) Proposal, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Stressed Si Papers, 1977-1980 (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - He3 Paper, Undated (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Kim Katris Notes, Undated (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Perry Hackins Documents, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Bill Dalton Notes, Undated (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - BASD-SIRTF Telescope Instrument Changeout and Cryogen Replenishment (STICCR) Study, 1985-11 (Box 44)
  - Paul Graf Documents, 1982 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Dan Briotta Documents, 1987 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - John McCarthy Documents, 1980-1984 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Field Minutes, 1987 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Letters, 1989 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Budgets, 1985 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - VAX(?) Correspondence, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - IRTF(Infrared Telescope Facility) Hawaii, 1980 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - AAVSO (American Association of Variable Star Observers) Documents, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - VLBI (?) Network Users Group Documents, 1978-1979 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Partly Reduced Data, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Cornell Forms, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Hot Stuff, 1979-07 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - James Houck Documents, 1987 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - C-141 Documents, 1981-11 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Fabry Perot Documents, 1982 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - IRAS Proposal Prep, 1986-1987 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Letters, 1985 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Astro III Notes, Undated (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Old Notes, Undated (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Radio Proposal, 1985 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Tom Roelig Papers, Undated (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Ron Keith Papers, 1982 (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Mark Dow Papers, 1985 (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - Dave Lind Papers, Undated (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - Mark Shure Papers, 1982 (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - IRAS Peer Review, 1987 (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - Mexico Papers, 1987 (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Paris Papers, 1987 (Box 45, Folder 29)
  - London Papers, 1987 (Box 45, Folder 30)
  - Hawaii Meetings, 1986-1987 (Box 45, Folder 31)
  - HST Review, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 32)
  - IRAS Proposal, 1985-1988 (Box 45, Folder 33)
  - Implications of Science, 1987-1988 (Box 45, Folder 34)
  - AMES Tester, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 35)
  - FPTC (?), 1980 (Box 45, Folder 36)
  - AMB (?), 1969 (Box 45, Folder 37)
  - Arizona Testing, 1978-1979 (Box 45, Folder 38)
  - AMES Focal Plane Testing, 1973-1976 (Box 45, Folder 39)
  - AMES Focal Plane Testing, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 40)
  - Ge:Be Progress Reports, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 41)
  - Ge:Ga Materials Proposal, 1978-1979 (Box 45, Folder 42)
  - Testing at Cornell Reports, 1978-1982 (Box 45, Folder 43)
  - Focal Plane Array, 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 44)
  - Science Notes, 1979 (Box 45, Folder 45)
  - Focal Plane Tester Documents, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 46)
  - Focal Plane Tester Standard Ar., 1979 (Box 45, Folder 47)
  - Focal Plane Tester Documents Preliminary Design Review, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 48)
  - Focal Plane Tester Filters, 1979 (Box 45, Folder 49)
  - IRAS Optics, 1979 (Box 45, Folder 50)
  - IRAS Optics, 1980 (Box 45, Folder 51)
  - Internet Stimulators, 1979 (Box 45, Folder 52)
  - Focal Plane Tester Optics, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 53)
  - Focal Plane Tester Plans, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - T^3 Memoranda, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - FSS (?) Spikes, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Confirmation Papers, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Approved Slides, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Notes, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - News Reports, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Letters, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Far Infrared Sky Survey Experiment (FIRSSE), 1977-1978 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Total Flux Experiments, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Misc. Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Misc. Proposals and Reports, 1973-1975 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Misc. Papers, 1970-1976 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Misc. Blueprints, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - TOST (?) Reports, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Calibration Notes, Undated (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Gyro Test Notes, Undated (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Forms, Undated (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Contamination Notes, Undated (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - IOC Remains, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - SubSystem Validation Plans, 1982 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Weekly Project Reports, 1982 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - SSTSUR Memo, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - Nature Paper, Undated (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - Preamps (?) etc., 1981-1982 (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - Scattered Light Notes, 1980 (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - Zody Light Correspondence, 1982 (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - FPA Weekly Status, 1981 (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - Cryogenics Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - Charged Part Reports, 1978-1981 (Box 46, Folder 30)
  - IRAS RadHits, 1980 (Box 46, Folder 31)
  - MOS FETS (?) Papers, 1978-1979 (Box 46, Folder 32)
  - J-230 FET Module (?) Papers, 1980 (Box 46, Folder 33)
  - Band2 Problem, 1982 (Box 46, Folder 34)
  - Inputs from J. Houck, 1980-1982 (Box 46, Folder 35)
  - Mold Constraint Papers, 1977-1978 (Box 46, Folder 36)
  - Blacks and Off-Axis Papers, 1982 (Box 46, Folder 37)
  - Optics and Crosstalk Papers, 1981 (Box 46, Folder 38)
  - Filters and Spectral Resp. Memoranda, 1978-1981 (Box 46, Folder 39)
  - Clean Data Test, 1982-06 (Box 46, Folder 40)
  - Hybrids Correspondence, Undated (Box 46, Folder 41)
  - Electronics Reports, 1980 (Box 46, Folder 42)
  - Electronic Gains, Etc., 1981 (Box 46, Folder 43)
  - Band #1 Refit, 1982 (Box 46, Folder 44)
  - Band #4 Refit, 1980-1981 (Box 46, Folder 45)
  - VSAS Calibration, 1981 (Box 46, Folder 46)
  - Close Galaxies Papers, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 47)
  - FPA General California Institute of Technology Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - FPOA (?) Correspondence, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - IOC Papers, 1983 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Engineering Reports, 1983 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Band #4 Refit, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - AO Program Documents, 1983 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - IOC Tests, 1982-1983 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - LRS Raw Data Analysis, 1983 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - SIRTF Reports, 1981-1982 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Nonlinear RL's Notes, 1978 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - IRAS Electronics, 1978 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Rockwell Information, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - FPOA (?) Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - PE Mirror Report, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous Papers, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Alignment Notes, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Photon Background, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Macro Correspondence, 1982 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Sky Flux Papers, 1979-1982 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Science Analysis, 1982 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - AO's (except CG) (?), 1981-1982 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Observation Request Forms, etc., Undated (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - Deep Sky Papers, 1982 (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - Galactic Plane Papers, 1981-1982 (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - Sensitivity Charts, Undated (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - Telescope Requirements, 1982 (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - Mold Memoranda, 1982 (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - TSY Status, 1982 (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - IRX General, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - TSY General, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 30)
  - Quarterly Reviews, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 31)
  - Science Team Materials, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 32)
  - Short Mission, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 33)
  - Calibration Notes, 1980-1982 (Box 47, Folder 34)
  - Conway's Telephone (Box 47, Folder 35)
  - DAX Report, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 36)
  - Science Team Materials, 1982 (Box 47, Folder 37)
  - Catalogs (Astro), 1982 (Box 47, Folder 38)
  - Limiting Flux, 1982 (Box 47, Folder 39)
  - Observing Plan, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 40)
  - Post-Mission Notes, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 41)
  - Final Data, 1982 (Box 47, Folder 42)
  - Extended Mission Notes, Undated (Box 47, Folder 43)
  - Post Docs Advertising, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 44)
  - Soft Issues, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 45)
  - SDAS (?) Task Team, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 46)
  - Asteroids Papers, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 47)
  - Flight Time Notes, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 48)
  - Project Minutes, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 49)
  - Project Minutes, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 50)
  - Project Minutes, 1982 (Box 47, Folder 51)
  - Science Team Minutes, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 52)
  - IRAS Science, 1982-1983 (Box 47, Folder 53)
  - Active Galaxies, 1983 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Pure Science, 1976-2982 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - IRAS Paper, 1979-1980 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Rockwell Progress Reports, 1978-1979 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Rockwell Progress Reports, 1978-1979 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Strategic Plans, 1983-1994 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Astrophysics Subcommittee Misc. Plans, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - Astrophysics Subcommittee Talk Materials, 1993-08-02 (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - Nasa Astrophysics Subcommittee Minutes (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - Astrophysics Subcommittee Agendas, 1992-06 (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - Astrophysics Subcommittee Agendas, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - Astrophysics Subcommittee Agendas, 1989-09 (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - Astrophysics Subcommittee Agendas, 1990-01 (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - Astrophysics Subcommittee Agendas, 1989-05 (Box 49, Folder 27)
  - Astrophysics Count Subcommittee Agendas, 1989-05 (Box 49, Folder 28)
  - Strategic Plans, 1994-1999 (Box 49, Folder 29)
  - Astrophysics Subcommittee Report, 1995 (Box 49, Folder 30)
  - Astrophysics Subcommittee Agendas, 1995-02 (Box 49, Folder 31)
  - Infrared Radio MOWG (?), 1992-06 (Box 49, Folder 32)
  - Infrared Radio MOWG (?), 1991-10 (Box 49, Folder 33)
  - Infrared Radio MOWG (?), 1991-05 (Box 49, Folder 34)
  - MOWG (?), 1991-02 (Box 49, Folder 35)
  - MOWG (?) follow-up, 1991-02 (Box 49, Folder 36)
  - Infrared Radio MOWG (?), 1990-06 (Box 49, Folder 37)
  - Infrared Radio MOWG (?), 1990-10 (Box 49, Folder 38)
  - Nasa Astrophysics Subcommittee Minutes, 1993-04-13-1993-04-14 (Box 49)
  - Infrared Radio MOWG (?) Follow Up, 1990-06 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Infrared Radio MOWG (?), 1990-05 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Infrared Radio MOWG (?), 1990-02 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Infrared Radio MOWG (?), 1990-02 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - MOWG (?), 1989-06 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Infrared Radio MOWG (?), 1989-11 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Important Issues- Space Science Advisory Committee Meeting, 1995-03 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Space Science Advisory Committee Handouts, 1995-03 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Space Science Advisory Committee Minutes, 1994-09 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Space Science Advisory Committee Presentations, 1994-04 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Space Science Advisory Committee Presentations, 1994-01 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Space Science Advisory Committee Minutes, 1993-1994 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - SSAAC.693 (?), Undated (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Space Science Advisory Committee Strategic Planning, Undated (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Readings for John, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - MO+DA (?) Fact Finding Meeting, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Space Sciences Applications and Advisory Committee Presentations, 1993-06 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - April Astrophysics Subcommittee Meeting, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Astrophysics Subcommittee Minutes, 1992-1993 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Space Science Applications and Advisory Committee, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Space Science Applications and Advisory Committee Meeting Minutes, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - Space Science Applications and Advisory Committee Presentations, 1993-06 (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - AMOWG Strategic Planning, 1993-08 (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - Space Science Applications and Advisory Committee, 1993-05-21 (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - Requirements Review I Transparencies, 1986-08-14 (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - General IRS Talk Transparencies, 1992-06-26 (Box 50, Folder 26)
  - Infrared Science @ Science Working Group, 1993-04 (Box 50, Folder 27)
  - Spectrograph Transparencies, 1993-12-02 (Box 50, Folder 28)
  - ASNY Talk, 1989 (Box 50, Folder 29)
  - ASNY Talk, 1987 (Box 50, Folder 30)
  - Tuesday Lunch Talk, Undated (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - A-671 Spectroscopy, Undated (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Caltech Transparencies, 1994-05-04 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Science Transparencies, 1992 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Infrared Science Overview, 1994-10-10 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Ball Science Team Transparencies, 1999 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Infrared Science Minutes Boulder (Ball), 1999 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Ball Minutes, 1993-11-18 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - GeBIB Workshop @ Rockwell, 1993-11-17 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Stressed Ge:Ga Transparencies, 1993-08 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Optical Des Color Negatives, 1993-08 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Ge Stress and Bib Photographs, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - 2.5-5 microns GRISM (?), 1993 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Pointing Reconstruction, 1995-07-25 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - SPIE (?) Originals, 1995 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - SPIE (?) Orlando, 1995 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Shuttle Infrared Telescope Facility Memorandum, 1993-08 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Science Working Group Correspondence, 1994-05 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Bahcall Process Transparencies, Undated (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Payload Proposals, 1994-02 (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Evaluation of Si:As and Si:Sb Blocked Impurity Band Detectors for SIRTF and WIRE, 1995-06-12 (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - Si:As BIBIB Radiation Testing Transparencies, 1995-01-25 (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - Washington Talk Science Working Group Presentation, 1994-09 (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Infrared Science Update, 1994-09-10 (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - Viewgraphs Red Book, 1995 (Box 51, Folder 25)
  - Big Bang: Friends of Astronomy Transparencies, 1995-05 (Box 51, Folder 26)
  - JVC Science Working Group Vu-Graphs, 1995-05 (Box 51, Folder 27)
  - Science Working Group Correspondence, 1996-01 (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - Space Science Advisory Committee Trip, 1996-03 (Box 51, Folder 29)
  - Infrared Science Mut Tucson Presentation, 1996 (Box 51, Folder 30)
  - Science Working Group Correspondence, 1996-05 (Box 51, Folder 31)
  - SIRTF-Cornell Echelle Spectrograph (SCORE)-AAS (?), 1996 (Box 51, Folder 32)
  - SIRTF-Cornell Echelle Spectrograph (SCORE)-AAS (?) Handouts, 1996 (Box 51, Folder 33)
  - AAS Poster Duplicates, 1997-01 (Box 51, Folder 34)
  - Science Working Group Options, 1996-05 (Box 51, Folder 35)
  - Space Science Advisory Committee Presentations, 1996-09-1996-10 (Box 51, Folder 36)
  - Space Science Advisory Committee Meeting Washington, DC Presentations, 1996 (Box 51, Folder 37)
  - Jim's Preliminary Non-Advocate Review View graphs, 1996 (Box 51, Folder 38)
  - Preliminary Non-Advocate Review View Graphs, 1996-06-26 (Box 51, Folder 39)
  - SIRTF Preliminary Non-Advocate Review, 1996 (Box 51, Folder 40)
  - System Design Team #1 Viewgraphs Cornell and Ball, 1996-08-20 (Box 51, Folder 41)
  - System Design Team Viewgraphs, 1996-08-20 (Box 51, Folder 42)
  - System Design Team Kickoff, 1996-08 (Box 51, Folder 43)
  - Science Working Group Documents, 1996 (Box 51, Folder 44)
  - PORR (?) Viewgraphs, 1996-12 (Box 51, Folder 45)
  - SiPDR Preparation, 1997-02 (Box 51, Folder 46)
  - Si:Xx PDR (?), 1997-02-20 (Box 51, Folder 47)
  - FSRR (?) Presentation, 1997-02 (Box 51, Folder 48)
  - Observatory Requirements Review, 1997-02 (Box 51, Folder 49)
  - Infrared Science Team Minutes, 1997-03 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Infrared Science Recosting Minutes, 1997-05 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Infrared Science Cold PDR and Team Meeting, 1997-08 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Harold Reitsema Triton Observation, 1997 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - System PDR (?), 1997-09 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Short-Low CDR (?), 1998-02 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Infrared Science Status, 1998-04 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Infrared Astronomy at Cornell, 1998-05 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Final Report- Analysis of Galactic and Extragalactic IRAS, Undated (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Infrared Detectors and Mechanisms Proposal, 1991-11 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - "Moderate Resolution Spectroscopy for the Space Infrared Telescope Facility" Paper, 1986 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - 16-38 Micron Spectroscopy of NGC 7027, 1979 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - A Liquid-Helium-Cooled Grating Spectrometer for Far Infrared Astronomical Observations Paper, 1979 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - 16-39 Micron Spectroscopy of Oxygen-Rich Stats Paper, 1979 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - The Galactic Center: 16-30 Micron Observations and the 18 Micron Extinction Paper, 1981-05 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Medium-Resolution Spectra of M82 and NGC 1068 from 16 to 30 Microns Paper, 1980-12-01 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - 16-30 Micron Spectroscopy of Titan Paper, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - A Far-Infrared Emission Feature In Carbon-Rich Stars and Planetary Nebulae, 1981-08 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Abundances of Argon, Sulfur, and Neon in Six Galactic HII Regions from Infrared Forbidden Lines Paper, 1981 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - The 1-mm Brightness Temperature of Titan, 1981 (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - Observations of the 30 Micron Feature in IRC + 10216 Paper, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - Detection of the 33.47 Micron Line in the Orion Nebula-T Paper, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - The Suppression of Charged-Particle Induced Noise in Infrared Detectors Paper, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - Cooled Grating Infrared Spectrometer for Astronomical Observations Paper, Undated (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - A New Black Paint for Cryogenic Infrared Applications, Undated (Box 52, Folder 25)
  - Observations of the Infrared Fine-Structured Lines of SII at 18.71 Microns in Four H II Regions Paper, 1982-11 (Box 52, Folder 26)
  - Abundances in Five Nearby Galactic HII Regions from Infrared Forbidden Lines Paper, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Cryogenic Testing of Stepper Motors Paper, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 28)
  - Positional Repeatability Measurements of Stepper Motors at Cryogenic Temperatures, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 29)
  - Detection of Sulfur in the Galactic Center Paper, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 30)
  - Determinations of SIII, OIV, and NeV Abundances in Planetary Nebulae from Infrared Lines Paper, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 31)
  - O IV Temperature Determination for NGC 7662 Paper, 1983 (Box 52, Folder 32)
  - A Helium -3 Cooled Bolometer System for One Millimeter Continuum Observations Paper, 1983 (Box 52, Folder 33)
  - Detection of the Micron Line in the Planetary Nebula NGC 6543, 1984-06 (Box 52, Folder 34)
  - The Electron Density in M82 from the SIII Mid-Infrared Line Ratio Paper, 1984 (Box 52, Folder 35)
  - The Infrared Astronomical Satellite Mission Paper, 1984 (Box 52, Folder 36)
  - Discovery of a Shell Around Alpha Lyrae Paper, 1984 (Box 52, Folder 37)
  - IRAS Observations of Shapley-Ames Galaxies Paper, 1984 (Box 52, Folder 38)
  - IRAS Images of the Galactic Center Paper, 1984 (Box 52, Folder 39)
  - IRAS Observations of the Diffuse Infrared Background Paper, 1984 (Box 52, Folder 40)
  - Infrared Cirrus: New Components of the Extended Infrared, 1984 (Box 52, Folder 41)
  - Unidentified Point Sources in the IRAS Minisurvey Paper, 1983 (Box 52, Folder 42)
  - The IRAS Minisurvey, 1984 (Box 52, Folder 43)
  - Infrared Galaxies in the IRAS Minisurvey, 1984 (Box 52, Folder 44)
  - Observations of Comet IRAS-Araki-Alcock Paper, 1984 (Box 52, Folder 45)
  - The Electron Density in the Galactic Center as Derived from the SIII 18.71/33.47 Micron Line Paper, 1984 (Box 52, Folder 46)
  - Early Results from the Infrared Astronomical Satellite Paper, 1984 (Box 52, Folder 47)
  - Cryogenic Telescope on the Infrared Astronomical Satellite, 1984 (Box 52, Folder 48)
  - A Far Infrared Cooled Grating Spectrometer for the Kuiper Airborne Observatory Paper, 1984 (Box 52, Folder 49)
  - The IRAS Galaxy 0421+040P06: An Active Spiral Galaxy with Extended Radio Lobes Paper, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 50)
  - Origin of the Solar System Dust Bands Discoved by IRAS Paper, 1984-12 (Box 52, Folder 51)
  - Unidentified IRAS Sources: UltraHigh Luminosity Galaxies Paper, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 52)
  - Infrared Astronomy After IRAS Paper, 1986 (Box 52, Folder 53)
  - Moderate Resolution Spectroscopy for the SIRTF Paper, Undated (Box 52, Folder 54)
  - The Most Luminous Far-Infrared Extra-Galactic Sources, 1987 (Box 52, Folder 55)
  - Detection of Silicon in the Galactic Center Paper, 1986-06 (Box 52, Folder 56)
  - The IRAS View of the Extragalactic Sky Papers, 1987 (Box 52, Folder 57)
  - A Very Deep IRAS Survey at 1=97^0, b=30^0, 1987 (Box 52, Folder 58)
  - The Distribution of Si II in the Galactic Center Papers, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 59)
  - A Very Deep IRAS Survey: Constraints on the evolution of Starburst Galaxies Papers, 1987 (Box 52, Folder 60)
  - Test Results with Rockwell SiBIBIB Hybrid Arrays Papers, 1987 (Box 52, Folder 61)
  - Infrared Detectors for Space Applications Papers, 1987-04 (Box 52, Folder 62)
  - A Very Deep IRAS Survey at the North Ecliptic Pole Paper, 1987 (Box 52, Folder 63)
  - Multifrequency Survey of the Intergalactic Cloud in the M96 Group Paper, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 64)
  - A Very Deep IRAS Survey III Paper, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 65)
  - Identifying Galaxies in the Zone of Avoidance Paper, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 66)
  - Space Infrared Spectroscopy of Atoms and Ions Paper, 1993-01 (Box 52, Folder 67)
  - The High-Excitation Region of NGC 7027 Paper, 1992 (Box 52, Folder 68)
  - Dwarf Cepheid Variables Stars: A Study of CY Aquarii Paper, 1992 (Box 52, Folder 69)
  - The Infrared Spectrum of the Optically Thin Dust Shell of V705 Cassiopeia Paper, 1993-1995 (Box 52, Folder 70)
  - The Zodiacal Background in the IRAS Data Paper, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 71)
  - IRAS Solar System Dust Bands: A Testable Hypothesis, Undated (Box 52, Folder 72)
  - The OSS Cold Focus Position, 1980-05-27 (Box 52, Folder 73)
  - The Galactic Center: Abundances, Densities, Excitation and Temperature, Undated (Box 52, Folder 74)
  - The Design of Small Ln2 Shielded LHE Research DeWars, 1983-02 (Box 52, Folder 75)
  - Electron Temperature in NGC 1068 from Combined UV Infrared Observations of OIV and NeV, Undated (Box 52, Folder 76)
  - Cornell Radiation Testing, 1981-05 (Box 52, Folder 77)
  - Blank Field Point Sources in IRAS Mini-Survey, Undated (Box 52, Folder 78)
  - Protostars and/or Heavily Obscured Objects, 1981-02 (Box 52, Folder 79)
  - Density in a Planetary Nebula from the SIII IR Line Ratio, 1985-01 (Box 52, Folder 80)
  - A Fabry-Perot Interferometer for High-Resolution Mid-Infrared Spectroscopy, 1985-01 (Box 52, Folder 81)
  - Planetary Nebulae Studies Summary of Results, 1981-02 (Box 52, Folder 82)
  - Bahcall Follow-On, 1989-1991 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Cover Page/Divider Pages, 1996 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Title Page/Table of Contents, 1996 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - IRS (Infrared Spectrometer) Overview, Undated (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - IRS (Infrared Spectrometer) Science, Undated (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Instrument Design, Undated (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Detector Development, Undated (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Test Bench Module, Undated (Box 53, Folder 8)